<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.luisppb16.dbseed</id>
    <name>Database Seed Generator</name>
    <version>1.1.1</version>
    <vendor email="ironkrozz@gmail.com">Luis Pepe</vendor>
    <description>
        <![CDATA[
            A smart SQL seed generator that respects your schema's integrity.

            This plugin generates synthetic data by introspects your database's `DatabaseMetaData`.
            It automatically analyzes table dependencies, manages foreign keys, and resolves complex cycles using Tarjan's algorithm.
            Stop writing manual insert scripts for your test environments.
            <h2>Main Features</h2>
              <li>Schema introspection via DatabaseMetaData.</li>
              <li>Table sorting using Tarjan's algorithm to detect cycles.</li>
              <li>Synthetic data generation with DataFaker.</li>
              <li>Cycle handling with deferred constraints.</li>
              <li>Support for multiple databases with dynamic driver downloads.</li>
        ]]>
    </description>

    <change-notes>
        <![CDATA[
            <ul>
              <li><b>Migrate to Java 21:</b> The plugin has been fully migrated to Java 21, ensuring compatibility with the latest Java features and better performance.</li>
              <li><b>Select All Primary Keys Feature:</b> The PK selection dialog now allows selecting all primary keys at once, streamlining workflows when working with complex schemas.</li>
              <li><b>Exclude Columns Tab:</b> Added a user interface tab that lets users exclude specific columns from synthetic data generation, offering increased flexibility and customization for testing scenarios.</li>
              <li><b>UI Fixes and Improvements:</b> The cancel button in dialogs now works reliably. Minor interface enhancements and wording improvements were also made for better usability.</li>
              <li><b>Copyright and Minor Enhancements:</b> Copyright statements have been updated and minor bugs have been fixed for a smoother experience.</li>
              <li><b>Primary Key Selection Bug Fixes:</b> Several fixes were applied to the <code>PK Selection Dialog</code>, addressing stability and functional issues.</li>
            </ul>
        ]]>
    </change-notes>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <actions>
        <action id="SeedDatabaseAction"
                class="com.luisppb16.dbseed.action.SeedDatabaseAction"
                text="Database Seed Generator"
                description="Seeds the database with generated data.">
            <add-to-group group-id="ToolsMenu" anchor="last"/>
        </action>
    </actions>
    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <notificationGroup id="Database Seed Generator"
                           displayType="BALLOON"
                           isLogByDefault="true"/>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
